Rockhill, William Woodville, 1854-1914. William Woodville Rockhill papers (MS Am 2121): Guide.
William Woodville Rockhill papers,
- I. Correspondence and other papers
  - Smet de Naeyer, Comte de. Typescript (c.c.) of L.s.(Cte de Smet de Naeyer) to ["Ministre des Affair Etrangeres"; Bruxelles, 8 Aug 1904., (2484); 1l.
  - Smith, H. T. Typed L.s.(H. T. Smith) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Constantinople 10 Feb 1897., (2485); [4]p.
  - Smithers, George F. A.L.s.(Geo. F. Smithers) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chung King, 30 Dec 1896., (2486); ([4]p.)
  - Snodgrass, John Harold, 1870- Typed L.s.(John H.Snodgrass) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Moscow, 3 Dec 1913., (2486a); 1l.
    Enclosures: Typed Reports of "Emigration and Migration in Russi etc.;" 14l.; s.(John H.Snodgrass); Moscow, 28 Nov 1913.
  - Snodgrass, John Harold, 1870- Typed L.s.(John H. Snodgrass) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Moscow, 26 Jan 1914., (2487); 2l.
  - Societe de geographie, Paris. Ms.L.s.(Jules de Guerne) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 27 Fe 1895., (2488); ([1]p.)
  - Someillan, Louis. A.L.s. (Louis Someillan, Jr.) to Richard Olney;; Key West, 24 Feb [1897]., (2489); 1l.
  - Sone, viscount, Typed Memorandum(unsigned); [n.p., n.d.], (2490); 2l.
  - Sone, viscount. Newspaper Article; [n.p., n.d.], (2491); 1l.
  - Spencer, Arthur Coe, 1871- A.L.s. (Arthur C. Spencer) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington Jan 1903., (2492); 3l.
  - Sperry, Charles S. A.L.s.(C. S. Sperry) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Chefoo, 7 Jun 1901, (2493); 2l.
  - Sperry, Charles S. Typed Memorandum s.(C. S. Sperry) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; U.S.S. New Orleans, 3 Jun 1901., (2494); 2l.
  - Sperry, Charles S. Typed Extract from a letter by Captain C. S. Sperry; Kobe, 18 Feb 1902., (2495); 5l.
  - Sperry, Charles S. Typed L.s.(C. S. Sperry) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Newport, 5 May 1904., (2496); 1l.
  - Sperry, Charles S. A.L.s.(C. S. Sperry) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [Newport] 28 Dec [1904], (2497); ([4]p.)
  - Sperry, Charles S. A.L.s.(C. S. Sperry) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Manila, 8 Nov [1911], (2498); ([14]p.)
  - Stahel, Julius, 1825-1912. Transcript of L.s.(Alvey A. Adee) to [Julius] Stahel; Washington, 26 Sep 1904., (2499); ([4]p.)
    Also: Transcript of L.s.(J. Stahel) to John Hay; Washington, 24 Sep 1904 [2]p.
  - Stahel, Julius, 1825-1912. A.L.s.(J. Stahel) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 16 Nov 1904, (2500); ([3]p.)
  - Steenacken, J B A.L.s.(J.B.Steenacken) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 28 Feb 1896., (2500a); (1l.)
  - Sternburg, H A.L.s.(Sternburg) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; "The Weirs", [1903], (2500b); ([3]p.)
  - Sternburg, H A.L.s.(H.Sternburg) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; "The Weirs" 18 Jul 1900., (2500c); ([5]p.)
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin, 1833-1902. A.L.s.(B. F. Stevens) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 21 Sep 1895., (2501); 1l.
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin, 1833-1902. Typed L.s.(B. F. Stevens) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 4 Oct 1895., (2502); 1l.
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin, 1833-1902. Typed L.s.(B. F. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 5 Oct 1895., (2503); 2l.
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin, 1833-1902. Typed L.s.(B. F. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 14 Nov 1895., (2504); 2l.
  - Stevens, Benjamin Franklin, 1833-1902. Typed L.s.(B. F. Stevens) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 16 Sep 1898., (2505); 1l.
  - Stevens, D W A.L.s.(D.W.Stevens) to[William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 18 Jul 1894., (2505a); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tokio, 30 Aug 1902., (2506); ([14]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W.Stevens) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 16 Jun 1903., (2507); ([3]p.)
    Enclosure: Transcript of Telegram (unsigned); Tokio, 16 Jun 1903. 1l.
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 6 Aug 1903., (2508); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W.Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 8 Aug 1903., (2509); ([3]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. Typed L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 18 Jul 1904., (2510); ([2]p.)
    Enclosure: Manuscripts in Chinese characters; 3l.
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 24 Aug 1904., (2511); ([3]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 26 Aug 1904., (2512); ([3]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 17 Sep 1904., (2513); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 24 Nov 1904., (2514); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 6 Feb 1905., (2515); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 26 Feb 1905, (2516); ([8]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W.Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 18 Jun 1905., (2517); ([12]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 23 Jul 1905, (2518); ([8]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 20 Feb 1906, (2519); ([8]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 19 Mar 1906, (2520); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 2 Sep 1905., (2521); ([8]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 11 Nov 1906, (2522); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 10 Dec 1906, (2523); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 13 Jan 1907, (2524); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 14 Jan 1907, (2525); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W.Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 12 May 1907., (2526); ([4]p.)
  - Stevens, D. W. A.L.s.(D. W. Stevens) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Seoul, 28 Jul 1907., (2527); ([8]p.)
  - Stevens, (B. F.) Brown. Typed L.s.(B. F. Stevens Brown, J.C.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 27 Jun 1914., (2528); 1l.
    Enclsoure: Ms. Statement of [William Woodville Rockhill]. 1l.
  - Stevens, (B. F.) Brown. Typed L.s.(B. F. Stevens Brown by Henry J. Brown) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 11 Sep 1914., (2529); 1l.
  - Stewart, Francis Edward, 1853- Typed L.s.(F. E. Stewart) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; Detroit, 10 Dec 1895., (2530); 2l.
  - Stimpson, Herbert Baird, 1869- A.L.s.(H. B. Stimpson) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, [190-?], (2531); ([3]p.)
  - Stimpson, Herbert Baird, 1869- A.L.s.(H. B. Stimpson) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore, [190-?], (2532); ([1]p.)
  - Stoddard, Charles Warren, 1843-1909. A.L.s.(Chs. Warren Stoddard) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 21 Dec [1892]., (2533); ([2]p.)
  - Stoddard, Charles Warren, 1843-1909. A.L.s.(Chs. Warren Stoddard) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [Washington] 8 Feb [1897]., (2534); ([2]p.)
  - Stolypin, Petr Arkaderich, 1862-1911. A.L.s.(P. Stolypin) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [n.p.] 10/23 Sep 1909., (2535); ([1]p.)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher, 1880- Typed L.s.(Lyman Beecher Stowe) to Norman Dwight Harris; New York, 18 May 1920., (2536); 2l.
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher, 1880- Typed L.s.(Lyman Beecher Stowe) to Norman Dwight Harris; Garden City, 16 Jun 1920., (2537); 1l.
  - Storer, Bellamy, 1847-1922. A.L.s.(Bellamy Storer) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cincinnati, 18 Feb 1896., (2538); [2]p.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Havana, 8 Jul 1906., (2538a); ([2]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 18 Apr 1907., (2539); ([4]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 27 Apr 1907., (2540); 3l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 2 May 1907., (2541); ([2]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 14 May 1907., (2542); ([2]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 24 May 1907., (2543); ([6]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 14 Jun 1907., (2544); 3l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight, per A. W.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 9 Oct 1913., (2545); 1l.
  - Omitted from series., (2546)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 4 Jun 1907., (2547); ([5]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 9 Jul 1907., (2548); ([4]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 23 Jul 1907., (2549); 2l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Wd. Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 23 Sep 1907., (2550); 5l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 8 May 1908., (2551); 2l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Mukden, 10 May 1908., (2552); 2l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p., 11 May 1908], (2553); ([2]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 11 Dec 1910., (2554); 4l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Telegram s.(Straight) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; London, [1911], (2555); 1l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 13 Jan 1911., (2556); 1l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 25 Jun 1914., (2557); 2l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 30 Jun 1914., (2558); 2l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed Day Letter s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; New York, 13 Jul 1914., (2559); 1l.
    With A. Reply s.(Rockhill) at bottom.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed Night Letter s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill New York, 13 Jul 1914., (2560); 1l.
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. Typed L.s.(Willard Straight) to [William] [Woodville]Rockhill; New York, 17 Nov 1914., (2561); ([2]p.)
  - Straight, Willard, 1880-1918. A.L.s.(Willard Straight) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; [New York, 18 Feb 1915., (2562); ([2]p.)
  - Stroebel, Edward Henry, 1855-1908. A.L.s.(Edward H. Stroebel) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Quito, 15 Aug 1894., (2563); ([6]p.)
  - Stroebel, Edward Henry, 1855-1908. Typed L.s.(Edward H. Stroebel) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Santiago 6 Mar 1897., (2564); 1l.
  - Stroebel, Edward Henry, 1855-1908. Typed L.s.(Edward H. Stroebel) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 19 Feb 1902., (2565); 1l.
  - Straus, Oscar Solomon, 1850-1926. Typed L.s.(Oscar S. Straus) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; New York City, 19 Apr 1911., (2566); 1l.
  - Sun, Pao Chi. Cablegram s.(Sun Pao Chi) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Peking, 9 Dec 1914., (2567); 1l.
  - Swingle, Walter Tennyson, 1871- Typed L.s.(Walter T. Swingle) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 20 Aug 1909., (2568); 2l.
    Enclosure: Typed Memorandum on Mongolian alfalfa and some other important native plants of Mongolia and Western China; 10l.
  - Swingle, Walter Tennyson, 1871- Typed L.s.(Walter T. Swingle) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 5 Apr 1910., (2569); 3l.
  - Taft, William Howard, pres. U.S., 1857-1930. Typed L.s.(Wm. H. Taft) to William [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 11 Dec 1908., (2570); ([1]p.)
  - Taft, William Howard, pres. U.S., 1857-1930. Typed L.s.(Wm. H. Taft) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Cincinnati, 18 Jan 1909., (2571); ([1]p.)
  - Taft, William Howard, pres. U.S., 1857-1930. A.L.s.(Wm. H. Taft) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 24 Dec 1910., (2572); ([3]p.)
  - Taft, William Howard, pres. U.S., 1857-1930. Typed L.s. (Wm. H. Taft) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 21 Feb 1911., (2572a); (1l.)
  - Taft, William Howard, pres. U.S., 1857-1930. Typed L.s.(Wm. H. Taft) to William Woodville Rockhill; Washington, 21 Jun 1911., (2573); ([1]p.)
  - Taft, William Howard, pres. U.S., 1857-1930. Typed L.s.(Wm. H. Taft) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 28 Jun 1912., (2574); ([1]p.)
  - Tait, James Selwin, 1846-1917. Typed L.s.(J. Selwin Tait) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 24 Sep [1908]., (2575); 2l.
  - Tait, James Selwin, 1846-1917. Typed L.s.(J. Selwin Tait) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 26 Feb [1909]., (2576); 2l.
  - Takahira, Kogoro. A.L.s.(K. Takahiro) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 20 Jul 1903., (2577); ([1]p.)
  - Tarler, G Cornell. A.L.s.(G. Cornell Tarler) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Belin, 1 Apr 1912., (2578); ([3]p.)
  - Tarler, G Cornell. A.L.s.(G. Cornell Tarler) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Therapia, 18 Aug 1913., (2579); ([4]p.)
  - Taw Sein Ko. Typed L.s.(Taw Sein Ko) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Mandalay, 12 Dec 1906., (2580); 1l.
    Enclosed: Translation of Inscription. Also: Photostat of Inscription.
  - Taylor, H. A. Typescript of L.s.(H. A. Taylor) to "Secretary of State"; Washington, 28 Mar 1903., (2581); 1l.
  - Taylor, Jacob. A. Poem s.(Jacob Taylor); [n.p., n.d.], (2582); 1l.
  - Taylor, John R. M. A.L.s.(John R. M. Taylor) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Vienna, 20 Feb 1912., (2583); ([4]p.)
  - Taylor, John R. M. A.L.s.(John R. M. Taylor) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Vienna, 1 May 1912., (2584); ([4]p.)
  - Taylor, John R. M. A.L.s.(John R. M. Taylor) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Vienna, 11 May 1912., (2585); ([4]p.)
  - Taylor, John R. M. A.L.s.(John R. M. Taylor) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Vienna, 20 Jul 1912., (2586); ([3]p.)
  - Taylor, John R. M. A.L.s.(John R. M. Taylor) to [Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Washington 16 Jan 1915., (2587); ([4]p.)
    With autograph annotation by Edith Howell (Perkins) Rockhill
  - Taylor, Francis Edward. A.L.s.(F.E. Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 9 Jan 1902., (2588); ([4]p.)
  - Taylor, Francis Edward. Typed L.s.(F. E. Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 26 Mar 1902., (2589); 1l.
  - Taylor, Francis Edward. Typed L.s.(F. E.Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 5 Sep 1902., (2590); 4l.
  - Taylor, Francis Edward. A.L.s.(F. E. Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 10 Jul 1903., (2591); ([4]p.)
  - Taylor, Francis Edward. A.L.s.(F. E. Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 23 Nov 1904., (2592); ([4]p.)
  - Taylor, Francis Edward. A.L.s.(F. E. Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Hankow, 4 Apr 1914., (2593); ([1]p.)
    Enclosed: Typed Scheme for the abolition of Likin, etc.; [n.p., n.d.] 6l.
  - Taylor, L. A.L.s.(L. Taylor) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Blackheath, 31 May [1894]., (2594); ([3]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(Chas. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tientsin, 7 Feb 1906., (2595); ([5]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(Chas. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tientsin, 4 Jun 1906., (2596); 1l.
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 2 Feb 1908., (2597); ([3]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Cambridge, 15 Feb 1908., (2598); [2]p.
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(Charles D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 11 Feb 1909., (2599); 3l.
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Shanghai, 13 Feb 1909., (2600); [2]p.
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(Charles D.Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 15 Mar 1910., (2600a); ([10]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C.D.Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 13 Apr 1910., (2600b); [4]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C.D.Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 20 Oct 1910., (2600c); ([7]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C.D.Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 26 Dec 1910., (2600d); ([8]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C.D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 6 Feb 1911., (2601); ([5]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 23 Feb 1911, (2602); [2]p.
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. Typed L.s.(C.D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 12 Apr 1911., (2603); [2]p.
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C. D. Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 7 Oct 1911., (2604); ([4]p.)
  - Tenney, Charles Daniel, 1857-1930. A.L.s.(C.D.Tenney) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 18 Nov 1911., (2604a); ([4]p.)
  - Terrauch, Masatake, viscount. Typed Translation of "Japanese-Korean Memorandum"; [n.p.] 24 Jun 1910., (2605); 2l.
  - Thebaud, Joseph. A.L.s.(Jos. Thebaud) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Parterville, [1914], (2606); ([3]p.)
  - Thil, R. A.L.s.(R.Thil) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 4 Jul 1897., (2606a); ([3]p.)
  - Thil, R. A.L.s.(R. Thil) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Lure, 21 May 1904., (2607); ([2]p.)
  - Thil, R. A.L.s.(Colonel Thil) to William Woodville Rockhill; [La Mulotiere, par Langeais, 23 Mar 1912], (2608); [1]p.
    Includes on verso: Printed notice in re the "annuaire de notre promotion de St. Cyr". [1]p. In French.
  - Thil, R. A.L.s.(Colonel Thil) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; La Pree par Segnyp 10 May 1912., (2609); ([3]p.)
  - Thil, R. Typed L.s.(Colonel Thil) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Da Mulotiere par Langeais, 10 Aug 1912., (2610); ([4]p.)
  - Thil, R. A.L.s.(Colonel Thil) to William Woodville Rockhill; [La Mulotiere, par Langeais, 18 Apr 1914., (2611); ([1]p.)
    Includes: Printed notice of dinner to be given 23 May 1914, in Paris.
  - Thil, R. Printed notice to [William Woodville Rockhill]; [La Mulotiere, par Langeais] 19 Apr 1919., (2612); ([2]p.)
    In French. With autograph annotation s.(Colonel Thil)
  - Thil, R. A.L.s.(Colonel Thil) to [Edith Howell (Perkins) Rockhill]; La Mulotiere par Langeais, 28 May 1919., (2613); ([3]p.)
  - Thin, James. Printed bill filled out in ms. to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Edinburgh, 14 Mar 1911., (2614); 1l.
  - Thomas, M. A. A.L.s.(M. A. Thomas) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Stockholm, 23 Jun 1899., (2615); ([3]p.)
  - Thoron, Ward A.L.s.(Ward Thoron) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Paris, 15 Apr 1911., (2615a); ([8]p.)
  - Tingle, Edward William Stephens. A.L.s.(E. W. S. Tingle) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Philadelphia, 21 Jul 1900., (2616); ([2]p.)
  - Tingley, C. A. Resolution (unsigned) to [Thomas C. Rockhill]; Philadelphia, 11 Mar 1854., (2617); ([1]p.)
  - Tingley, C. A.L.s.(C. Tingley) to [Thomas] C. Rockhill; [Philadelphia], 11 Mar 1854., (2618); ([1]p.)
  - Tingley, C. Ms.L.s.(C.Tingley) to Mary Rockhill; Philadelphia, 30 Apr 1855., (2619); ([1]p.)
  - Tolstoy, D. A.L.s.(D. Tolstoy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 1/14 Apr 1911., (2620); ([2]p.)
  - Tolstoy, D. A. Postcard s.(D. Tolstoy) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 8 Jan [1913]., (2621); [1]p.
  - Toucher, A. A.L.s.(A. Toucher) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [n.p.] 24 Oct 1905., (2622); ([2]p.)
  - Tower, Charlemagne, 1848-1923. Typescript of Telegram s.(Tower) to [John Hay]; Petersburg, 9 Feb 1900., (2623); 1l.
  - Townsend, Laurence. Ms.L.s.(Laurence Townsend) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Vienna, 24 Oct 1896., (2624); ([8]p.)
  - Tralliz, S T A.L.s.(S.T.Tralliz) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Baltimore 24 Mar 1887., (2624a); ([4]p.)
  - Tripp, Bartlett, 1842-1911. A.L.s.(Bartlett Tripp) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Vienna, 30 Oct 1896., (2625); ([2]p.)
  - Troubetzkai, Gregoire. A.L.s.(Gregoire Troubetzkai) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Moscow, 11/26 Apr 1911., (2626); ([4]p.)
  - Troubetzkai, Gregoire. A.L.s.(Gregoire Troubetzkai) to [William Woodville Rockhill]; Vassilievskoie, 8/21 Jun [1911], (2627); ([2]p.)
  - True, A. C. Typed L.s.(A.C. True) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Washington, 5 Oct 1914., (2628); 1l.
  - True, Rodney Howard, 1866- Typed L.s.(Rodney H. True) to Walter Hough; Washington, 21 Apr 1904., (2629); 1l.
    With A. Note s.(Walter Hough) to [William Woodville] Rockhill at bottom.
  - Trubner co., London. A.L.s.(Trubner Co.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 22 Aug 1882., (2630); ([1]p.)
  - Trubner Co., London. A.L.s.(Trubner Co.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 4 Sep 1882., (2631); ([2]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. A.L.s.(Trubner Co.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 16 Sep 1882., (2632); ([2]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. A.L.s.(Trubner Co.) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 7 Oct 1882., (2633); ([1]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. Ms.L.s.(N. Trubner) to [William] Woodville Rockhill; London, 1 Dec 1882., (2634); ([2]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. Ms.L.s.(N. Trubner) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 19 Oct 1883., (2635); ([2]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. Ms.L.s.(N. Trubner) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; London, 2 Nov 1883., (2636); ([2]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. A.L.s.(Trubner co.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 10 May 1884., (2637); ([1]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. A.L.s. (Trubner Co.) to [William] [Woodvlle] Rockhill; London, 14 May 1884., (2638); ([1]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. A.L.s. (Trubner Co.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 19 Jun 1884., (2639); ([2]p.)
  - Trubner co., London. Ms.L.s. (Trubner Co.) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; London, 4 Feb 1887., (2640); ([2]p.
  - Tsai [?] Typescript (c.c.) of Agreement; Tientsin, 14 Apr 1908., (2641); 8l.
  - Tsai, Shoukie Ms.L.s. (Tsai Shoukie) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Tientsin, 23 Aug 1905., (2642); ([2]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville Rockhill and Edith Howell (Perkins)] Rockhill; Peking, 8 Jan 1914., (2643); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 11 Jan [1914]., (2644); ([2]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 14 Jan 1914., (2645); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 15 Jan [1914], (2646); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William] [Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 19 Jan 1914., (2647); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; Peking, 20 Jan 1914., (2648); ([2]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 8 Mar [1914], (2649); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 13 Mar [1914], (2650); ([2]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 16 Mar [1914], (2651); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 17 Mar [1914], (2652); ([1]p.)
  - Tsai, Ting Kan, 1861- A.L.s. (Tsai Ting Kan) to [William Woodville] Rockhill; [Peking] 19 Mar [1914], (2653); ([1]p.)